{
    "subject": "resource/Cruz_Diablo",
    "predicate": "property/language",
    "object": "resource/Spanish_language",
    "human_readable": "The language of Cruz Diablo is Spanish.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9868829846382141,
            "question": "Is Spanish the official language of Cruz Diablo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9297234416007996,
            "question": "Are there any other languages spoken in addition to Spanish in Cruz Diablo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9138219952583313,
            "question": "How important is the Spanish language to the culture of Cruz Diablo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8794368505477905,
            "question": "What language is spoken in Cruz Diablo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8340985774993896,
            "question": "Are there any regional variations within the Spanish spoken in Cruz Diablo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7523977756500244,
            "question": "Would someone from a Spanish-speaking country easily understand people in Cruz Diablo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7332708239555359,
            "question": "What are the linguistic influences on the language of Cruz Diablo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6166670322418213,
            "question": "If someone wants to communicate with people in Cruz Diablo, what language should they learn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.567309558391571,
            "question": "What is the primary language used in daily life within Cruz Diablo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5586023926734924,
            "question": "Does the use of Spanish in Cruz Diablo have any historical significance?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The language of Cruz Diablo is Spanish.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7212_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary language used in daily life within Cruz Diablo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7212_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If someone wants to communicate with people in Cruz Diablo, what language should they learn?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7212_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the linguistic influences on the language of Cruz Diablo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7212_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7212_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7212_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7212_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7212_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7212_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7212_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7212_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7212_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7212_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7212_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context mentions the book \"La Cruz del Diablo\" by Gustavo Adolfo Becquer, which indicates that the language of \"Cruz Diablo\" is indeed Spanish."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}